# This file should contain all the record creation needed to seed the database with its default values.
# The data can then be loaded with the rails db:seed command (or created alongside the database with db:setup).
#
# Examples:
#
#   movies = Movie.create([{ name: 'Star Wars' }, { name: 'Lord of the Rings' }])
array = [
  {answer: "329685174471932586856471923293856417568714392714329658932568741147293865685147239", question: "320005100000000500800000020200006000008700300700309658002508040107093000685040200", progress: "320005100000000500800000020200006000008700300700309658002508040107093000685040200"},
  {answer: "483179625179625834625834791834791256791256348256348917917562483348917562562483179", question: "480070020009000800020000791800700050791250340006040017000002400308900500000003000", progress: "480070020009000800020000791800700050791250340006040017000002400308900500000003000"},
  {answer: "798124536365897214142563987987412365421356879653789142214635798879241653536978421", question: "090000506065000010042060087007012360001300079000780002000030000000041003506900020", progress: "090000506065000010042060087007012360001300079000780002000030000000041003506900020"},
  {answer: "325689174174352986698471325986147253253968741741235869417523698869714532532896417", question: "005000074100002080690400305006007050200908040041000800007500608800700002030890000", progress: "005000074100002080690400305006007050200908040041000800007500608800700002030890000"},
  {answer: "395178624264935817187624593718246935426359178539781246953817462642593781871462359", question: "390170020264005000100000003708206005006300178009001240050800000000090700000060300", progress: "390170020264005000100000003708206005006300178009001240050800000000090700000060300"},
  {answer: "475961823916823574832574619328457961754196382169382457283745196691238745547619238", question: "400900020906003504800070010000050901050006000109000050003700090000208040540619008", progress: "400900020906003504800070010000050901050006000109000050003700090000208040540619008"},
  {answer: "659183247472659831183724965831247659596831472724596318318472596965318724247965183", question: "609003000002050030003720965800240600590030470700006008000402000905008020000005000", progress: "609003000002050030003720965800240600590030470700006008000402000905008020000005000"},
  {answer: "698215437743986521215743869374698152869521743521374986986152374437869215152437698", question: "608000007040006020015703860300690102800020040500000000900152070030000010100030008", progress: "608000007040006020015703860300690102800020040500000000900152070030000010100030008"},
  {answer: "523691874169784253847352196784235961352169748916478532235916487478523619691847325", question: "023001000009000003040000090000005901002109708006408532000000400008523609690040000", progress: "023001000009000003040000090000005901002109708006408532000000400008523609690040000"},
  {answer: "864713529295468317317925486952846173648371295173592864529684731486137952731259648", question: "004710509095408007310900406000000000040300005073002060009600030080007000700259000", progress: "004710509095408007310900406000000000040300005073002060009600030080007000700259000"},
  {answer: "961254378378169524245387196196542837524873619837691452619425783452738961783916245", question: "901050008370160004005087000006502000020070009830000050010420700000700901083900000", progress: "901050078370160004005087000006502007020070009837000050010420700000700901783900000"},
  {answer: "826471953174935826395286741417359682539862174682714395741593268268147539953628417", question: "826001953004000020000006700407309600530060004002700000000003200200000030050008417", progress: "826001953004000020000006700407309600530060004002700000000003200200000030050008417"},
  {answer: "849312657132657894567894123756948231213576948984123576675489312321765489498231765", question: "000000650100007004007894003700908000013500900900003506675009010020005000008200700", progress: "000000650100007004007894003700908000013500900900003506675009010020005000008200700"},
  {answer: "981346752527189436436257981198463275752891643643572198364725819275918364819634527", question: "000046052520109400030000980090003270052001000600002100000700010200900304019000500", progress: "000046052520109400030000980090003270052001000600002100000700010200900304019000500"},
  {answer: "321875946469312857857964132132758694946123785785649213213587469578496321694231578", question: "021005006000310857807060000000000090046000705700040210013080400070400001004200008", progress: "021005006000310857807060000000000090046000705700040210013080400070400001004200008"},
  {answer: "365728149872941563941653827287194635536872491194365278728419356653287914419536782", question: "365000140072040560040003000200100000000870090000000208000409006603200010009036780", progress: "365000140072040560040003000200100000000870090000000208000409006603200010009036780"},
  {answer: "423165798897342615651978324342516987165897243789234156978423561234651879516789432", question: "020165098897300010000970020300016000160800240000230050008400500000000079006000000", progress: "020165098897300010000970020300016000160800240000230050008400500000000079006000000"},
  {answer: "897614253461523879352789416978146325523897641614235987235978164146352798789461532", question: "007610000400023870000009006008100320020807000014005007035000064006300000700001032", progress: "007610000400023870000009006008100320020807000014005007035000064006300000700001032"},
  {answer: "142689357689735142573421968735214689896357421421896573968573214357142896214968735", question: "100000000089000140570421960005010689000007001400800003908500200000000000010960705", progress: "100000000089000140570421960005010689000007001400800003908500200000000000010960705"},
  {answer: "349675812765128439821943756934756128576281394182439567657812943493567281218394675", question: "309000810700000400000903700000056008076280300002000000600010040003060280218090075", progress: "309000810700000400000903700000056008076280300002000000600010040003060280218090075"},
  {answer: "291643587857192643463758192912364758634875219578219364346587921785921436129436875", question: "291003080800100600063058000900004700000005009000009000300007921085900030100406800", progress: "291003080800100600063058000900004700000005009000009000300007921085900030100406800"},
  {answer: "679324815324185976851967342967432158432518769185796423796243581518679234243851697", question: "000020005024085906850007340007030100030000000100006420706203000010070030000801090", progress: "000020005024085906850007340007030100030000000100006420706203000010070030000801090"},
  {answer: "736158294294763851185492736673581429518924673429637185367815942851249367942376518", question: "736050094204060800080400006003001029500000000400030180000000000050240367040300500", progress: "736050094204060800080400006003001029500000000400030180000000000050240367040300500"},
  {answer: "812596734437812956596374218128965473965743821374128695281659347659437182743281569", question: "002506730037000900096074008000900000000000800004128005080009007009030182040200060", progress: "002506730037000900096074008000900000000000800004128005080009007009030182040200060"},
  {answer: "371985246426371958598426317264713895713859624985264731859642173137598462642137589", question: "001080200400370908090006017000000800013059004000200701059600000000508000642030009", progress: "001080200400370908090006017000000800013059004000200701059600000000508000642030009"},
  {answer: "257163849163849572498725316984257163572631498631498725725316984849572631316984257", question: "050063009003000070008000310900250160570001400031008020700000000040070001306980200", progress: "050063009003000070008000310900250160570001400031008020700000000040070001306980200"},
  {answer: "596748123213596784487321695132965478874213569965487312748132956321659847659874231", question: "096000000003006700000301600000005008870013069000007310008000950321050840600800030", progress: "096000000003006700000301600000005008870013069000007310008000950321050840600800030"},
  {answer: "695142378241387695378596124124873569837965412569421837956214783412738956783659241", question: "005140000000080605000000000100870560030960002509400830906010080002000056700059040", progress: "005140000000080605000000000100870560030960002509400830906010080002000056700059040"},
  {answer: "618342759579168234324759816861423597957681342432597168186234975795816423243975681", question: "010340009070068204320050006860400097950000000400007100000234005000010003203000000", progress: "010340009070068204320050006860400097950000000400007100000234005000010003203000000"},
  {answer: "521487369639512874847369512963125748152874693784693125478936251215748936396251487", question: "001407060630002074000300500000005040000070090004090000070000201205708036090251007", progress: "001407060630002074000300500000005040000070090004090000070000201205708036090251007"},
  {answer: "328795164164238759759614283832957416975146328416382975641823597597461832283579641", question: "308095064064000000000014200032900016070100300016382070000020500500000802000009000", progress: "308095064064000000000014200032900016070100300016382070000020500500000802000009000"},
  {answer: "172453896968271543354986217217534689435869721896712354721345968543698172689127435", question: "070003806908071040054900000000500680000009700006000354721040000003600102080100000", progress: "070003806908071040054900000000500680000009700006000354721040000003600102080100000"},
  {answer: "412589367376142589859367421598736142124958736763214958637421895241895673985673214", question: "410500007300000000009367420500700002024008700763014008000020090201090600000600000", progress: "410500007300000000009367420500700002024008700763014008000020090201090600000600000"},
  {answer: "514798362987623451623451879145987623879236514236514798451879236798362145362145987", question: "000090002000020000023450000040900623070036014030004708401800000098000105000040907", progress: "000090002000020000023450000040900623070036014030004708401800000098000105000040907"},
  {answer: "769138524318425697452679831831254769245796183976381452524967318697813245183542976", question: "069000000008405007450000001031200709005706083900001050000007010000800245083002000", progress: "069000000008405007450000001031200709005706083900001050000007010000800245083002000"},
  {answer: "932518647467392185581476239158764392746923851293185476329851764674239518815647923", question: "900500007060090085081406039000700090040003001200005400009801000004030500010040023", progress: "900500007060090085081406039000700090040003001200005400009801000004030500010040023"},
  {answer: "927865341413729568685314927568143792792658134341297856134972685856431279279586413", question: "920000340000000000600304000500100002000658000040207806130070605050400070200086013", progress: "920000340000000000600304000500100002000658000040207806130070605050400070200086013"},
  {answer: "317694285694825371582173496469582713258317964731469852825731649946258137173946528", question: "300600080004025371500000006469080000008307000001069002020001040900008030100000520", progress: "300600080004025371500000006469080000008307000001069002020001040900008030100000520"},
  {answer: "924351768513876492876924135249513687768249351135768924351687249492135876687492513", question: "004300000500070402806020035009003080700000300130008024000000200090130076007490010", progress: "004300000500070402806020035009003080700000300130008024000000200090130076007490010"},
  {answer: "927483165843615279165729438438561792279348651651972384516297843384156927792834516", question: "000000160003615270005709000000500090200300650051000080000200840380000020090830506", progress: "000000160003615270005709000000500090200300650051000080000200840380000020090830506"},
  {answer: "695314287827569134143827965569431872314782659782956341278695413956143728431278596", question: "600000287820069004043820905009031000304700050000000040208095003000003700000000006", progress: "600000287820069004043820905009031000304700050000000040208095003000003700000000006"},
  {answer: "693218475218574963574369128369821754821457639457936281745693812936182547182745396", question: "003000075018004903070009100000801000821050000450036080040600010900100540000000306", progress: "003000075018004903070009100000801000821050000450036080040600010900100540000000306"},
  {answer: "269135478351478269478926135513784692692351784784269351135847926926513847847692513", question: "069000400001070009408000035500004092000300084000009351000000020006510000840602013", progress: "069000400001070009408000035500004092000300084000009351000000020006510000840602013"},
  {answer: "681297534453681297729453681816972345534816972297534816168729453345168729972345168", question: "681007530003000200020450601006072000004010070000030800008000050340068000972000100", progress: "681007530003000200020450601006072000004010070000030800008000050340068000972000100"},
  {answer: "283169475916574823457328196691457238745832961328916754574283619832691547169745382", question: "000100005906004003007020190000000208040032060008016000000000609830690507160700080", progress: "000100005906004003007020190000000208040032060008016000000000609830690507160700080"},
  {answer: "134678529592413876867259314341786952678592431925134687786925143259341768413867295", question: "130600500500410006800059310001080000000500001000100607086020000009300760000807205", progress: "130600500500410006800059310001080000000500001000100607086020000009300760000807205"},
  {answer: "167234985958761342243985761716342859324859617895617423671423598589176234432598176", question: "167030905950060040003005700700000009000850010000617420000403008009000030432000000", progress: "167030905950060040003005700700000009000850010000617420000403008009000030432000000"},
  {answer: "943812765128756493675394821439128576756943182281567349394281657567439218812675934", question: "040002765020056003675304001000120500700940080000000049300000607000000000812005000", progress: "040002765020056003675304001000120500700940080000000049300000607000000000812005000"},
  {answer: "137825469258496173964137285496713852825649731713582694371258946649371528582964317", question: "130020069258000000964000000000713052000040701010500600001008000049300500002900010", progress: "130020069258000000964000000000713052000040701010500600001008000049300500002900010"},
  {answer: "394127568721865439856349217439271856685493721172658943217586394943712685568934172", question: "090120068720805409000049200400270000080000001000650003010500090000000080568004002", progress: "090120068720805409000049200400270000080000001000650003010500090000000080568004002"},
  {answer: "715348926962175834384926175629517483843692517157834692296751348571483269438269751", question: "000040920960005830004000070000500083800600007057000602096700300501003000030009051", progress: "000040920960005830004000070000500083800600007057000602096700300501003000030009051"},
  {answer: "428316759795842361631957248316579824957428136284163975842631597163795482579284613", question: "020006009090042301030000208010079000900000036204100900000030007003705402500204000", progress: "020006009090042301030000208010079000900000036204100900000030007003705402500204000"},
  {answer: "514689273723514986689372154968237541451968732372451869145896327896723415237145698", question: "010009273003000080600070154908230000000000700000050000140096000800000405237140600", progress: "010009273003000080600070154908230000000000700000050000140096000800000405237140600"},
  {answer: "875261349934587612126349587493758261612934758587126934349875126261493875758612493", question: "005060040900000010120000080003008061000030700080106900000805100200490800700602493", progress: "005060040900000010120000080003008061000030700080106900000805100200490800700602493"},
  {answer: "254197386386254971719863425863542719542971863197638254971386542638425197425719638", question: "050000006380004000019003025803000010042901860007030000000380542030020007005700000", progress: "050000006380004000019003025803000010042901860007030000000380542030020007005700000"},
  {answer: "716329845845176923392854167584761392671293584239548716167932458458617239923485671", question: "700309840800100020302000167000700090670000004000540010060900400058007230020400000", progress: "700309840800100020302000167000700090670000004000540010060900400058007230020400000"},
  {answer: "932465781456817923718923546187392654329546178564781392645178239871239465293654817", question: "900005080056000000018023540080300000320000100500701002605008209000030060003654000", progress: "900005080056000000018023540080300000320000100500701002605008209000030060003654000"},
  {answer: "593762148276184395184593267762841539935627814841935726627418953359276481418359672", question: "090062140000080000080503060700041030005607800800900000620010900009000401410050002", progress: "090062140000080000080503060700041030005607800800900000620010900009000401410050002"},
  {answer: "623947185974851632815326947236794518158632794749185263497518326581263479362479851", question: "020040180004800030000306007006700000058600090700180260000510306501260070000000050", progress: "020040180004800030000306007006700000058600090700180260000510306501260070000000050"},
  {answer: "358276491276491583491583762914835627583762914762914835149358276627149358835627149", question: "008076090070400000400003000900800600503002914000900030140358070600009350000607000", progress: "008076090070400000400003000900800600503002914000900030140358070600009350000607000"},
  {answer: "854617932293485176761932485617329854548176329932854761485761293176293548329548617", question: "004010902090080006061000005600009050500076320902004701000001003000203040000040607", progress: "004010902090080006061000005600009050500076320902004701000001003000203040000040607"},
  {answer: "479563821821749536536281794182497653947635182653812479218974365365128947794356218", question: "400500001821049006000080704000400000007000102603810009200900300065008940090006000", progress: "400500001821049006000080704000400000007000102603810009200900300065008940090006000"},
  {answer: "697528413528314679314976582976285341285143967143769258769852134431697825852431796", question: "097000410520004670004000500070080300205100907043009008060002100030600000800001006", progress: "097000410520004670004000500070080300205100907043009008060002100030600000800001006"},
  {answer: "147239586293658417685741923714392865329586174568417239932865741471923658856174392", question: "107200500090050010005000003000002000300080074060017230902800040071900058000070390", progress: "107200500090050010005000003000002000300080074060017230902800040071900058000070390"},
  {answer: "872516934516349728934728516493872651287651493651934872728165349165493287349287165", question: "870500904000009020900728000490800050007000093050030870000060309100400007300080100", progress: "870500904000009020900728000490800050007000093050030870000060309100400007300080100"},
  {answer: "928614537375829164164735928753982641641573289289461375416357892892146753537298416", question: "028004507000009064060730008003080040000503000200000000016307890002140003537000000", progress: "028004507000009064060730008003080040000503000200000000016307890002140003537000000"},
  {answer: "562198734437652981189347526374265198891734652625819473918473265256981347743526819", question: "560008700400052001009007020304000100000000002600819003010400060000080047700500819", progress: "560008700400052001009007020304000100000000002600819003010400060000080047700500819"},
  {answer: "942381576813675924756429831429813657567294183138756492381567249294138765675942318", question: "900380076010675004000000001400003050007090180000000000300067209290108000600042010", progress: "900380076010675004000000001400003050007090180000000000300067209290108000600042010"},
  {answer: "253948617671325984894716523167532849489671235325894176716253498532489761948167352", question: "050008000001000004804706003000532040089070000000090006706003008002009760040107350", progress: "050008000001000004804706003000532040089070000000090006706003008002009760040107350"},
  {answer: "639851742158742369247369518963518427724693185815427693396185274581274936472936851", question: "600850042050700009007369500003500007020600005805420003000100200001200900400000001", progress: "600850042050700009007369500003500007020600005805420003000100200001200900400000001"},
  {answer: "568173429294685173731942685317429856685731294942856731173294568856317942429568317", question: "508000000204085000700900600300009050605700004042000001103200560000010902400560300", progress: "508000000204085000700900600300009050605700004042000001103200560000010902400560300"},
  {answer: "457281396128936475936457218745128963693745182812693754369574821281369547574812639", question: "007080006020036070000400200745120000090000180810000754300570800000009000504000609", progress: "007080006020036070000400200745120000090000180810000754300570800000009000504000609"},
  {answer: "961384275384275619752196438196438527438527961275619843527961384843752196619843752", question: "901384200080205000002190408090008007030000060205000043000900000803700096000000702", progress: "901384200080205000002190408090008007030000060205000043000900000803700096000000702"},
  {answer: "213695847965784123487123956321956478748231569596847231132569784659478312874312695", question: "000000047000700003087003950021006008040200060500040001132069780009408010000010000", progress: "000000047000700003087003950021006008040200060500040001132069780009408010000010000"},
  {answer: "385421679124679358697583421769835214412796583538214796241967835853142967976358142", question: "305420009004079308697003000700830010000000080500000700200900005003100907000008042", progress: "305420009004079308697003000700830010000000080500000700200900005003100907000008042"},
  {answer: "139587624264931587578246193913875246426319875857462931785624319391758462642193758", question: "130507024000901500508046090000800000400019000050002030700000009390700060002103008", progress: "130507024000901500508046090000800000400019000050002030700000009390700060002103008"},
  {answer: "381726945549831267762459318813672594627945831495183726954318672276594183138267459", question: "000000000540001260060009008010072500000040801005080020000000672206000180138060409", progress: "000000000540001260060009008010072500000040801005080020000000672206000180138060409"},
  {answer: "395824716176359824284167359953482671842716935761935482428671593617593248539248167", question: "005804010000050000000060009000402600802700030760000080008000593010590200509240067", progress: "005804010000050000000060009000402600802700030760000080008000593010590200509240067"},
  {answer: "983465721564721938127938546271893654839546172645172893398654217712389465456217389", question: "000060021500720000020900540070000050009046070605102090308004200002309000006000089", progress: "000060021500720000020900540070000050009046070605102090308004200002309000006000089"},
  {answer: "986372541451698327372451968514986732723514896869723154237145689698237415145869273", question: "900000001051690020370051908000900700020004096800700000030000089608030400105060000", progress: "900000001051690020370051908000900700020004096800700000030000089608030400105060000"},
  {answer: "621453789345978621978621453897162345162345978534897162216534897453789216789216534", question: "620400000040070020970000050000160005062000908000807000216030090003709206700010004", progress: "620400000040070020970000050000160005062000908000807000216030090003709206700010004"},
  {answer: "379215468152864973486793125864937512793152846521648397648379251215486739937521684", question: "000000060100000900000700000860937010703050040500640300040000201010006709007521084", progress: "000000060100000900000700000860937010703050040500640300040000201010006709007521084"},
  {answer: "562847139913652487748193562625784391487319625139265874256478913391526748874931256", question: "002000100003052400008090500025004000480309600000265004000078903090000008000030256", progress: "002000100003052400008090500025004000480309600000265004000078903090000008000030256"},
  {answer: "348615792297438156516792438651927384729384561834156927165279843972843615483561279", question: "000605700090400056510090008000900300729000000030100007060200043970043005403000200", progress: "000605700090400056510090008000900300729000000030100007060200043970043005403000200"},
  {answer: "534971682628435719791826354453719826862354197179268543345197268917682435286543971", question: "000070000008030700790820050053019806002300100070208003045100060900000030080500070", progress: "000070000008030700790820050053019806002300100070208003045100060900000030080500070"},
  {answer: "581692437743185629296473815437518296815269374962347158629734581374851962158926743", question: "000090430003085609200400000400008006810069304000007058009000080074050060150020000", progress: "000090430003085609200400000400008006810069304000007058009000080074050060150020000"},
  {answer: "859213674312764985467895231985132467231647598746958123123476859598321746674589312", question: "800010600310000985400090000080000000000047590000008103003070000590320746674000300", progress: "800010600310000985400090000080000000000047590000008103003070000590320746674000300"},
  {answer: "318542967769381542524967813245796381697138254183254796976813425452679138831425679", question: "310000000700000500004960800005700001600130204000200796006803400450000030800025009", progress: "310000000700000500004960800005700001600130204000200796006803400450000030800025009"},
  {answer: "765239841814756392329841567293184756657923184148675239481567923576392418932418675", question: "765030040010750302000000067003004700000000000100600039401060000500302008902408600", progress: "765030040010750302000000067003004700000000000100600039401060000500302008902408600"},
  {answer: "849163257725948361613275984572489136984631725361752498498316572257894613136527849", question: "040100000705008061600200004000409006000030725061002000098300502050004010030500800", progress: "040100000705008061600200004000409006000030725061002000098300502050004010030500800"},
  {answer: "781364925295718364463592187178643259529187643346925871952871436634259718817436592", question: "080000925005708000403002187000043200029000603046005001050800030000209000007400000", progress: "080000925005708000403002187000043200029000603046005001050800030000209000007400000"},
  {answer: "612489753894573162573261849735612984126894375948735216489357621261948537357126498", question: "612009703000073100570060800005010004000094305048030016080350600060000000000100000", progress: "612009703000073100570060800005010004000094305048030016080350600060000000000100000"},
  {answer: "521384697843697521769215438152438769384769152976521843215843976697152384438976215", question: "021000690000697000009200400102400000080009102070000043200803070000102300400906010", progress: "021000690000697000009200400102400000080009102070000043200803070000102300400906010"},
  {answer: "468197532719532468253468719325846971971253846846719253197325684532684197684971325", question: "408007030010002008253008019305046000001050046846010000007005000000000007000001305", progress: "408007030010002008253008019305046000001050046846010000007005000000000007000001305"},
  {answer: "946857231312469785578231469231946578857123946694785123785312694469578312123694857", question: "040857200002400005000000009001906070050103000000080003705002604009570300023090007", progress: "040857200002400005000000009001906070050103000000080003705002604009570300023090007"},
  {answer: "785216439934578126621493758857162943216934875349785612162349587493857261578621394", question: "005006009030000100001493750000002043010034000009705002062009080000800000570600094", progress: "005006009030000100001493750000002043010034000009705002062009080000800000570600094"},
  {answer: "735912846921486357846375921357291468468537219219648573573129684684753192192864735", question: "730002006901080300840370900007001000060007200000600503500020080000003102092004005", progress: "730002006901080300840370900007001000060007200000600503500020080000003102092004005"},
  {answer: "738964152152837946946251873873649215694512387215378694387496521469125738521783469", question: "000904002002807000906001070803000005600012307200300004007400020009000038500080460", progress: "000904002002807000906001070803000005600012307200300004007400020009000038500080460"},
  {answer: "856379142421865973973124856397241685142658397685793214214586739739412568568937421", question: "050000040420805903900124850000040600002058000080703200200000700030000008560030020", progress: "050000040420805903900124850000040600002058000080703200200000700030000008560030020"},
  {answer: "728634159591782643364951287915278436287463591643195872436519728159827364872346915", question: "708604000590700043000900007000008400000063501600095002030510708009000000002300015", progress: "708604000590700043000900007000008400000063501600095002030510708009000000002300015"},
  {answer: "689217453172534689534689217345896172896172534721345896217453968453968721968721345", question: "080200453172004000500600007040800102090002500700305890200000008000008020960700000", progress: "080200453172004000500600007040800102090002500700305890200000008000008020960700000"},
  {answer: "926374158473581296851296374518629437269437815734158629347815962185962743692743581", question: "900070100073001200000290000018020407060000000734008009000010900005000740092703081", progress: "900070100073001200000290000018020407060000000734008009000010900005000740092703081"},
  {answer: "924513867513678924867924351492351786786492135351867492678249513135786249249135678", question: "920510800000070004867920000400001006000400100050800400008249003130080009040000600", progress: "920510800000070004867920000400001006000400100050800400008249003130080009040000600"},
  {answer: "859721643127364895346895721598172364271436589463589172634958217985217436712643958", question: "800700003007000895040090001000170064000400009463500070000958000005007000712003050", progress: "800700003007000895040090001000170064000400009463500070000958000005007000712003050"},
  {answer: "965183427724956183381742956247695318659318742813274695138427569472569831596831274", question: "060000400700900103001700006240000000050008702000070095038420069002509030006030004", progress: "060000400700900103001700006240000000050008702000070095038420069002509030006030004"},
  {answer: "728964135649153782315287469531728694964315827872496351287649513496531278153872946", question: "720060100009000700305200469030008604064310000800096000000000013000030008050870006", progress: "720060100009000700305200469030008604064310000800096000000000013000030008050870006"},
  {answer: "528347169374916258961825734743691825285734916619582473196258347437169582852473691", question: "020007000004910000060000030043601800205730016000080400100258300000069502800000600", progress: "020007000004910000060000030043601800205730016000080400100258300000069502800000600"},
  {answer: "478192536291356478536874912847921653653748291129563847784219365365487129912635784", question: "400092006000300470500870902000001600650040200100560007080210300360000009002000004", progress: "400092006000300470500870902000001600650040200100560007080210300360000009002000004"},
  {answer: "634279185185364972729581634297158346346927851851436729972815463518643297463792518", question: "000070100100300070009000000090050040300927801050030009072800003018640000403092010", progress: "000070100100300070009000000090050040300927801050030009072800003018640000403092010"},
  {answer: "148965723273418596569372184814659237956723841327184965732841659695237418481596372", question: "000005703000000000560372080010600007906000000027104065030800609000007400081590070", progress: "000005703000000000560372080010600007906000000027104065030800609000007400081590070"},
  {answer: "619482537842753169735691248284537691573916482961824375196248753357169824428375916", question: "010002000042753000030601208004000001000006000000000305106208703007060804008005910", progress: "010002000042753000030601208004000001000006000000000305106208703007060804008005910"},
  {answer: "147583269835692714692714358583269471714358926269471835926147583471835692358926147", question: "007500260000000704092014008580009400010358006060400000020000083070005002050026000", progress: "007500260000000704092014008580009400010358006060400000020000083070005002050026000"}
]


array.each do |data|
  Puzzle.create(data)
end